Hello, I'm Aaron. A London based digital designer.

PROFILE

Since graduating in 2011 I've been helping companies communicate online. That has required a lot of wireframing, prototyping, designing and testing – but most of all learning. My recent research has focused on responsible responsive web design and prototyping.

EXPERIENCE

SEPTEMBER 2013 - PRESENT

Digital Designer Addison Group

At Addison Group my role is to take a creative lead on digital projects, from initial concept through to delivery. Projects vary, but regularly involve interpreting brand guidelines, working on wireframes, creating prototypes, overseeing junior designers and presenting the creative outcomes to the client.

It's important to me that my designs are accessible and intuitive to users, so I work closely with the development team to ensure the best possible implementation.

NOVEMBER 2012 - SEPTEMBER 2013

Digital Designer The Group

SEPTEMBER 2011 – NOVEMBER 2012

Junior Digital Designer The Group

EDUCATION

OCTOBER 2008 - JULY 2011

BA (Hons) Graphic Media University of Essex

Second-class honours, upper division (2:1)

SEPTEMBER 2006 – JUNE 2008

ND Graphic Design Digital Media Colchester Institute

http://aaronroot.net

EMAIL

mail@aaronroot.net

TELEPHONE

+44 7872037679